{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Advanced Systems Integration and Architecture",
    "Term": "Prefinals",
    "Title": "Customer Service (CS) Part 2",
    "LastModified": "20 November 2024",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "06 Handout 1 - 1"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "A billing must be created first before planning and releasing a request.",
      "answer": "This statement is FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE .",
        "This statement is FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "After the service order is released, the activities are executed and performed such as repair and maintenance.",
      "answer": "This statement is TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE .",
        "This statement is FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "A confirmation and technical completion are achieved to issue the accrued cost in the form of billing.",
      "answer": "This statement is TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE .",
        "This statement is FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "After the execution of activities are settled, then the business or service is completed.",
      "answer": "This statement is FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE .",
        "This statement is FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the FIRST step in Service Order Process?",
      "answer": "Service Order",
      "choices": [
        "Service Order",
        "Billing",
        "Good Issue",
        "Technical inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the SECOND step in Service Order Process?",
      "answer": "Planning and release",
      "choices": [
        "Planning and release",
        "Good receipt",
        "Repair",
        "Execution of activities"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the THIRD step in Service Order Process?",
      "answer": "Execution of activities",
      "choices": [
        "Execution of activities",
        "Business completion",
        "Service Order",
        "Business completion"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the FOURTH step in Service Order Process?",
      "answer": "Confirmation and technical completion",
      "choices": [
        "Confirmation and technical completion",
        "Service Order",
        "Technical inspection",
        "Billing"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the FIFTH step in Service Order Process?",
      "answer": "Billing",
      "choices": [
        "Billing",
        "Business completion",
        "Confirmation and technical completion",
        "Execution of activities"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the SIXTH step in Service Order Process?",
      "answer": "Business completion",
      "choices": [
        "Business completion",
        "Billing",
        "Confirmation and technical completion",
        "Execution of activities"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many steps does a Service Order Process have?",
      "answer": 6,
      "choices": [
        6,
        8,
        4,
        7
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "A customer repair order is initiated informing the business about a possible goods return due to a defect.",
      "answer": "This statement is FALSE .",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE .",
        "This statement is FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "A customer repair order is created and issued in the second step of Goods Return and Repair Process.",
      "answer": "This statement is TRUE .",
      "choices": [
        "This statement is TRUE .",
        "This statement is FALSE ."
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many steps does a Goods Return and Repair Process have?",
      "answer": 8,
      "choices": [
        6,
        8,
        4,
        7
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the FIRST step in Goods Return and Repair Process?",
      "answer": "Customer message",
      "choices": [
        "Customer message",
        "Customer repair order",
        "Good receipt",
        "Technical inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the SECOND step in Goods Return and Repair Process?",
      "answer": "Customer repair order",
      "choices": [
        "Customer repair order",
        "Good receipt",
        "Technical inspection",
        "Technical inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the THIRD step in Goods Return and Repair Process?",
      "answer": "Good receipt",
      "choices": [
        "Good receipt",
        "Technical inspection",
        "Repair",
        "Service order"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the FOURTH step in Goods Return and Repair Process?",
      "answer": "Technical inspection",
      "choices": [
        "Technical inspection",
        "Billing",
        "Good Issue",
        "Service order"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the FIFTH step in Goods Return and Repair Process?",
      "answer": "Repair",
      "choices": [
        "Repair",
        "Service order",
        "Good Issue",
        "Good receipt"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the SIXTH step in Goods Return and Repair Process?",
      "answer": "Service order",
      "choices": [
        "Service order",
        "Good receipt",
        "Good Issue",
        "Billing"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the SEVENTH step in Goods Return and Repair Process?",
      "answer": "Good Issue",
      "choices": [
        "Good Issue",
        "Service order",
        "Repair",
        "Technical inspection"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the EIGHTH step in the Goods Return and Repair Process?",
      "answer": "Billing",
      "choices": [
        "Billing",
        "Good receipt",
        "Technical inspection",
        "Repair"
      ],
      "reference": "06 Handout 1 - 2",
      "term": "Prefinals"
    }
  ]
}
